[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Do you have any way of knowing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "way", "of", "knowing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, it is interesting, Piers, just how difficult information has been to get.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "interesting", ",", "Piers", ",", "just", "how", "difficult", "information", "has", "been", "to", "get", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Do you feel in danger where you are now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "in", "danger", "where", "you", "are", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, you know, I think that we have to deal with the scientific facts here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "we", "have", "to", "deal", "with", "the", "scientific", "facts", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"]}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Clearly a pretty desperate situation, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Clearly", "a", "pretty", "desperate", "situation", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "It's desperate but Sanjay is correct, it's confused.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "desperate", "but", "Sanjay", "is", "correct", ",", "it", "'s", "confused", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, the building has been blown away the secondary containment on a couple of these places so you could in theory drop water in.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "building", "has", "been", "blown", "away", "the", "secondary", "containment", "on", "a", "couple", "of", "these", "places", "so", "you", "could", "in", "theory", "drop", "water", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "And Matthew, finally and very quickly, is the situation worse tonight than it was last night?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Matthew", ",", "finally", "and", "very", "quickly", ",", "is", "the", "situation", "worse", "tonight", "than", "it", "was", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What do you know about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "know", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "There have been reports that Saudi forces have been involved.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "have", "been", "reports", "that", "Saudi", "forces", "have", "been", "involved", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "And Wolf, what did she have to say about the ongoing crisis at the Fukushima nuclear plant in Japan, because it seems to be getting ever more dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Wolf", ",", "what", "did", "she", "have", "to", "say", "about", "the", "ongoing", "crisis", "at", "the", "Fukushima", "nuclear", "plant", "in", "Japan", ",", "because", "it", "seems", "to", "be", "getting", "ever", "more", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Yes, it's a catastrophe and she says it's minute by minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "catastrophe", "and", "she", "says", "it", "'s", "minute", "by", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wolf"], "LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What's behind it, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "behind", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "It's a good question because her job approval numbers in our latest CNN -- CNN poll, she's -- two-thirds of the American public give her favorable ratings.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "because", "her", "job", "approval", "numbers", "in", "our", "latest", "CNN", "--", "CNN", "poll", ",", "she", "'s", "--", "two-thirds", "of", "the", "American", "public", "give", "her", "favorable", "ratings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Do you have any latest news on that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "latest", "news", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, I really only know what we've put out on our Web site, Piers, and obviously, you know, I'm extremely worried for my four colleagues.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "really", "only", "know", "what", "we", "'ve", "put", "out", "on", "our", "Web", "site", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "obviously", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "extremely", "worried", "for", "my", "four", "colleagues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Can you quite believe what you're witnessing here?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "quite", "believe", "what", "you", "'re", "witnessing", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "RIEDMAN: No, I really can't.", "answer_tokens": ["RIEDMAN", ":", "No", ",", "I", "really", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "When you talk about the dominos, are they very different kinds of dominos we're seeing here or do you detect a common thread?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "talk", "about", "the", "dominos", ",", "are", "they", "very", "different", "kinds", "of", "dominos", "we", "'re", "seeing", "here", "or", "do", "you", "detect", "a", "common", "thread", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, the common thread is the aspiration of Arabs of all ages to want to run their own lives in a world where they can increasingly see how other people are living and see just how fracture behind they are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "common", "thread", "is", "the", "aspiration", "of", "Arabs", "of", "all", "ages", "to", "want", "to", "run", "their", "own", "lives", "in", "a", "world", "where", "they", "can", "increasingly", "see", "how", "other", "people", "are", "living", "and", "see", "just", "how", "fracture", "behind", "they", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Do you think there's any danger the House of Saud could fall?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "danger", "the", "House", "of", "Saud", "could", "fall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "You know, I don't want to make any predictions that the whole Saudi regime is going to fall but this is what I think is important to keep in mind, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "make", "any", "predictions", "that", "the", "whole", "Saudi", "regime", "is", "going", "to", "fall", "but", "this", "is", "what", "I", "think", "is", "important", "to", "keep", "in", "mind", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Saud"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Is this opportunity or could this go horribly wrong for them?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "opportunity", "or", "could", "this", "go", "horribly", "wrong", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "DT", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "You know, I think it's very understandable, Piers, that they would feel exactly the mixed emotions that you're describing.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "understandable", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "they", "would", "feel", "exactly", "the", "mixed", "emotions", "that", "you", "'re", "describing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "If you were sitting down, as I am, with Prime Minister Netanyahu tomorrow, what would you ask him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "sitting", "down", ",", "as", "I", "am", ",", "with", "Prime", "Minister", "Netanyahu", "tomorrow", ",", "what", "would", "you", "ask", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, I don't think he'd talk to me, but good luck.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "'d", "talk", "to", "me", ",", "but", "good", "luck", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Is that the prudent course of action?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "prudent", "course", "of", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, there's two things I would say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "two", "things", "I", "would", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "You can hardly blame him for wanting to see how things play out, can you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "hardly", "blame", "him", "for", "wanting", "to", "see", "how", "things", "play", "out", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Piers, let's take Egypt first.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "let", "'s", "take", "Egypt", "first", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "If you're Benjamin Netanyahu, what do you say to your people, not just about that incident, in terms of an appropriate response, but also in terms of this cargo ship which was seized apparently carrying a load of weapons to Gaza?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "Benjamin", "Netanyahu", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "your", "people", ",", "not", "just", "about", "that", "incident", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "an", "appropriate", "response", ",", "but", "also", "in", "terms", "of", "this", "cargo", "ship", "which", "was", "seized", "apparently", "carrying", "a", "load", "of", "weapons", "to", "Gaza", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "There's no question that any prime minister would have to speak first in the tones of grief and even anger about a horrific murder that we saw in the area.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "question", "that", "any", "prime", "minister", "would", "have", "to", "speak", "first", "in", "the", "tones", "of", "grief", "and", "even", "anger", "about", "a", "horrific", "murder", "that", "we", "saw", "in", "the", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Benjamin Netanyahu"], "LOCATION": ["Gaza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Rudy, what do you make of these appalling scenes in Japan?", "question_tokens": ["Rudy", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "these", "appalling", "scenes", "in", "Japan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, of course, like everyone, I'm shocked by what happened and I feel terrible for the Japanese people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "like", "everyone", ",", "I", "'m", "shocked", "by", "what", "happened", "and", "I", "feel", "terrible", "for", "the", "Japanese", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "In terms of how they have dealt with this disaster so far, do you think they've been doing the right things?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "how", "they", "have", "dealt", "with", "this", "disaster", "so", "far", ",", "do", "you", "think", "they", "'ve", "been", "doing", "the", "right", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "You know, I can't say because I'm not there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "say", "because", "I", "'m", "not", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Have you been as stunned as the rest of us by the way they have handled this?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "as", "stunned", "as", "the", "rest", "of", "us", "by", "the", "way", "they", "have", "handled", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "No, because I know them well.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "I", "know", "them", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Netanyahu"]}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "But there's a much bigger picture at play now, isn't there?", "question_tokens": ["But", "there", "'s", "a", "much", "bigger", "picture", "at", "play", "now", ",", "is", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Prime Minister Netanyahu is a remarkable man.", "answer_tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Netanyahu", "is", "a", "remarkable", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110316pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "How damaging would it be should Gadhafi win his battle, having murdered tens of thousands of his people by the time this finishes?", "question_tokens": ["How", "damaging", "would", "it", "be", "should", "Gadhafi", "win", "his", "battle", ",", "having", "murdered", "tens", "of", "thousands", "of", "his", "people", "by", "the", "time", "this", "finishes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Piers, from the outside, right now, it looks like Gadhafi every day is solidifying his position.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "from", "the", "outside", ",", "right", "now", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "Gadhafi", "every", "day", "is", "solidifying", "his", "position", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}]